oksingapore.com 2012-12-27

# Privacy-Jinqiao International Group Pte. Ltd. - Singapore manpower, study in Singapore, Singapore tourism, business, investigate and Singapore investment immigrant, Singapore summer camp. Various kinds of Singapore visa advisers, Singapore website construction, software development, plane design, customer service system,china & singapore culture dissemination

## 

Update  
2010-9-7 16:08:17 

JinQiao International Group is committed to protecting your privacy on the Internet. We believe that it is important for you to know what we do with your personal information. When it comes to consumer data collected electronically, JinQiao International Group will provide notice, choice, access and security in ways described below. In general, you, as our customer, can visit JinQiao International Group on the World Wide Web without having to reveal any personal information that you do not want to disclose.

Our web servers collect domain names and not the e-mail addresses. This information may be aggregated on a "no names" basis just to measure the number of visits, average time spent on the site, or pages viewed. Our web servers also seek (as many Web sites do) to place a "cookie" (a small data file) on your computer's hard drive which allows the server to recognize the computer when it visits again. This helps track statistical information about navigation through our site. This cookie is not used to obtain your name or any personal data, and the information that is tracked is used only for internal purposes, such as to improve site navigation. JinQiao International Group uses these data to measure the usage of, and improve the content of our sites.

In an effort to make your visit both efficient and safe, all transfers of personal information via this site meet JinQiao International Group rigorous Internet security standards.

Occasionally, our site may contain electronic links to other sites. In case you choose to go to those sites, their own privacy policy and privacy preferences will apply.

If you feel that the JinQiao International Group Web site ([http://www.oksingapore.com](http://www.oksingapore.com/)) is not abiding by its posted privacy policy, contact the Webmaster or send your concerns to the JinQiao International Group Headquarter,No 9 Jurong Town Hall Road iHUB #02-55 Singapore
